Leonard Everett Fisher Papers
© 2010 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Correspondence, undated, 1950-1999
  - Appearances, 1961-1999
    - Oldfield School, Fairfield, CT, 1971 (Box 81:291)
    - Barlow Mountain School Book Fair, 1971 April 23 (Box 81:292)
    - Green Farms School, Westport, CT, 1971 May (Box 81:293)
    - Trumbull Public Schools, Trumbull, CT, 1971 May 24 (Box 81:294)
    - Staples High School Career Clinic, Westport, CT, 1971 May 26 (Box 81:295)
    - New Canaan Country Day School, CT, 1971 October 21 (Box 81:296)
    - The Washington Post Book Fair, Washington D.C., 1971 November 9 (Box 81:297)
    - The Bi-Cultural Day School, Stamford, CT, 1971 November 19 (Box 81:298)
    - Notes on appearances / LEF did not appear, 1972 (Box 81:299)
    - New Canaan Historical Society, 1972 October 19 (Box 81:300)
    - Amherst College, Woodstock, CT, 1972 April 7 (Box 81:301)
    - Barlow Mountain School, Ridgefield, CT, 1972 April 18 (Box 81:302)
    - Northport Public Library, Northport, NY, 1972 April 22 (Box 81:303)
    - Green Farms School, 1972 May (Box 81:304)
    - Van Buren Moody School, Middletown, CT, 1972 June 5 (Box 81:305)
    - Union Free School, Northport, NY, 1972 June 19 (Box 81:306)
    - South Norwalk Public Library, South Norwalk, CT, 1972 July 14 (Box 81:307)
    - East School, New Canaan, CT, 1972 November 10 (Box 81:308)
    - Fairfield, CT, 1972 November 13 (Box 81:309)
    - The Washington Post Book Fair, Washington, D.C., 1972 November 15 (Box 81:310)
    - Notes on appearances / LEF did not appear, 1973 (Box 81:311)
    - Book Group of Darien Community Association, CT, 1973 January 23 (Box 81:312)
    - Payle School Book Fair, 1973 May 7 (Box 81:313)
    - 6th Annual Children's Book Festival, Hartford, CT, 1973 June 13 (Box 81:314)
    - Housatonic Community College, Westport, CT, 1973 September 10 (Box 81:315)
    - Connecticut Reading Conference, 1973 October 13 (Box 81:316)
    - The Washington Post Annual Book Fair, 1973 November 13 (Box 81:317)
    - NCTE / CBC Conference, 1973 November 24 (Box 81:318)
    - Notes on appearances / LEF did not appear, 1974 (Box 81:319)
    - Weston Public School, Weston, CT, 1974 January 7 (Box 81:320)
    - Meriden Public Library, Meriden, CT, 1974 February 27 (Box 81:321)
    - Central Connecticut State University, New Britain, 1974 March 14 (Box 81:322)
    - Barlow Mountain School, Ridgefield, CT, 1974 April 1 (Box 81:323)
    - Litchfield, CT, 1974 April 4 (Box 81:324)
    - Shepherd Glen School, Hamden, CT, 1974 April 18 (Box 81:325)
    - Staples High School, Westport, CT, 1974 April 26 (Box 81:326)
    - Green Farms Academy, Green Farms, CT, 1974 May 11 (Box 81:327)
    - Coleytown Junior High School, Westport, CT, 1974 May 29 (Box 81:328)
    - Fairfield University "Annual Sidewalk Art Show", 1974 June 13 (Box 81:329)
    - Southern Connecticut State College, New Haven, 1974 August (Box 81:330)
    - Fairfield Country Day School, 1974 November 1 (Box 81:331)
    - University of Bridgeport, 1974 November 4 (Box 81:332)
    - East School, New Canaan, CT, 1974 November 6 (Box 81:333)
    - Cuyahoga County Public Library, OH, 1974 November 12 (Box 81:334)
    - Coleytown Elementary School, Westport, CT, 1974 December 13 (Box 81:335)
    - List of appearances, 1975 (Box 81:336)
    - Notes on appearances / LEF did not appear, 1975 (Box 81:337)
    - Special Workshop, Westport, CT, 1975 January 3 (Box 81:338)
    - Richardson Independent School District, Texas, 1975 January 13 (Box 81:339)
    - Stamford Art Association, Stamford, CT, 1975 March 3 (Box 81:340)
    - Coleytown Landmark's Club visits LEF, 1975 April (Box 81:341)
    - Meet the Author Dya, NJLA, Atlantic City, NJ, 1975 April 24 (Box 81:342)
    - Western CT State College, Danbury, CT, 1975 May 5 (Box 81:343)
    - NEEMA Conference, Portsmouth, NH, 1975 May 8 (Box 81:344)
    - Barlow Mountain School, Ridgefield, CT, 1975 May 12 (Box 81:345)
    - IRA Convention, New York, NY, 1975 May 16 (Box 81:346)
    - Southern Connecticut State College, 1975 July-August (Box 81:347)
    - Essex Art Association, Essex, CT, 1975 July 28 (Box 81:348)
    - Wright State University, Dayton, Ohio, 1975 August (Box 81:349)
    - University of Hartford, 1975 August 4 (Box 81:350)
    - Bergen Country Day School Librarians Assoc., NJ, 1975 October 7 (Box 81:351)
    - Connecticut Reading Conference, Glastonbury, CT, 1975 October 25 (Box 81:352)
    - West School District, Unionville, CT, 1975 November 3 (Box 81:353)
    - New Hartford, Connecticut, 1975 November 17 (Box 81:354)
    - New Hartford, Connecticut, 1975 November 23 (Box 81:355)
    - East Farms Elementary School, Farmington, CT, 1975 December 2 (Box 81:356)
    - LEF did not appear / notes, 1976 (Box 82:357)
    - The Free Library of Philadelphia, PA, 1976 January 12 (Box 82:358)
    - Green Meadows Junior High School, Comack, NY, 1976 March 27 (Box 82:359)
    - Yankee Doodle Day, Cleveland Public Library, OH, 1976 April 10 (Box 82:360)
    - Appalachian St. University Language Arts Festival, 1976 April 22 (Box 82:361)
    - CLA Trumbull, CT, 1976 April 30 (Box 82:362)
    - Barlow Mountain School, Ridgefield, CT, 1976 May 11 (Box 82:363)
    - Hudson County School Media Association, NJ, 1976 May 19 (Box 82:364)
    - Fairfield Parent Library Volunteer Tea Group, CT, 1976 May 26 (Box 82:365)
    - Ox Ridge Elementary School, Darien, CT, 1976 June 9 (Box 82:366)
    - Reading Conference, Notre Dame Univ., MI, 1976 July 12 (Box 82:367)
    - ALA of Ohio, Columbus, Ohio, 1976 October 27 (Box 82:368)
    - Richardson, Texas, 1976 November 4 (Box 82:369)
    - Tilford Miller School, Wilton, CT, 1976 November 8 (Box 82:370)
    - Westport Public Schools, Westport, CT, 1976 (Box 82:371)
    - LEF did not appear / Miscellaneous correspondence, 1977 (Box 82:372)
    - Saugatuck Elementary School Book Fair, 1977 (Box 82:373)
    - Barlow Mountain School Book Fair, Ridgefield, CT, 1977 May 11 (Box 82:374)
    - Rhode Island Educational Media Association, RI, 1977 September 22 (Box 82:375)
    - The Holmes School, Darien, CT, 1977 September 28 (Box 82:376)
    - Clark Co., Farmingdale, NY, 1977 October 19 (Box 82:377)
    - Children's Books Northeast, Boston, MA, 1977 October 22 (Box 82:378)
    - Connecticut, 1977 November 15 (Box 82:379)
    - Commack Public Schools, Commack, New York, 1977 November 18 (Box 82:380)
    - Not finalized / LEF did not appear, 1978 (Box 82:381)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 82:382)
    - Greenwich Public Schools, CT, 1978 (Box 82:383)
    - Honeyhill School Book Fair, Norwalk, CT, 1978 April 18 (Box 82:384)
    - Meriden Careers Expo, Meriden, CT, 1978 April 19 (Box 82:385)
    - Barlow Mountain Elementary School Book Fair, CT, 1978 May 15 (Box 82:386)
    - Riverbank School, Stamford, CT, 1978 May 16 (Box 82:387)
    - Byram School, CT, 1978 May 17 (Box 82:388)
    - Rochester, NY, 1978 May 18 (Box 82:389)
    - Brookside School, Norwalk, CT, 1978 May 22 (Box 82:390)
    - Northport High School, Commack, NY, 1978 May 23 (Box 82:391)
    - SCOPE class visit's LEF's studio, 1978 June 3 (Box 82:392)
    - The University of Toledo, Toledo, Ohio, 1978 July 11 (Box 82:393)
    - Visit at LEF's studio, 1978 August (Box 82:394)
    - Stamford Art Association, Stamford, 1978 September 18 (Box 82:395)
    - 29th Annual Reading Conference, North Haven, CT, 1978 October 14 (Box 82:396)
    - American Assoc. of Univ. Women, Bridgeport, CT, 1978 October 22 (Box 82:397)
    - Fairview Park Library, Ohio, 1978 November 12 (Box 82:398)
    - Ellington Public Schools, 1978 November 20 (Box 82:399)
    - Honeyhill / McGrath School, S. Norwalk, CT, 1978 December 4 (Box 82:400)
    - Not finalized / LEF did not appear, 1979 (Box 82:401)
    - Library Media and Reading Motivation Inst., MD, 1979 January 6 (Box 82:402)
    - University of Southern Mississippi, 1979 March 1 (Box 82:403)
    - Oklahoma Library Association, Oklahoma, 1979 March 21 (Box 82:404)
    - Stamford Public Schools, CT, 1979 March 29 (Box 82:405)
    - Green Farms Elementary School, Westport, CT, 1979 April 2 (Box 82:406)
    - Hawkins Path School, Selden, Long Island, NY, 1979 April 4 (Box 82:407)
    - SLMS/NYLA Award, School Library Media Association, 1979 May 4 (Box 82:408)
    - Commack Union Free School District, NY, 1979 May 12 (Box 82:409)
    - Barlow Mountain School, 1979 May 15 (Box 82:410)
    - Daniels Farms School, Trumbull, CT, 1979 May 23 (Box 82:411)
    - Junior Women's Club of Monroe, Monroe, CT, 1979 May 23 (Box 82:412)
    - ALA Conference, 1979 June 26 (Box 82:413)
    - Westport Rotary Club, Westport, CT, 1979 August 7 (Box 82:414)
    - University of Maryland Library, Baltimore, MD, 1979 September 18 (Box 82:415)
    - New Canaan Book Fair, CT, 1979 October 23 (Box 82:416)
    - The University of Iowa, 1979 October 26 (Box 82:417)
    - Monroe Public Library, 1979 November 9 (Box 82:418)
    - Greater Cleveland International Book Fair, 1979 November 13 (Box 82:419)
    - The White House Conference on Library & Information, 1979 November 15 (Box 82:420)
    - Not finalized- LEF did not appear, 1980 (Box 83:421)
    - Publisher's Library Promotion Group, NY, 1980 January 15 (Box 83:422)
    - Drexel University, Philadelphia, PA, 1980 March 19 (Box 83:423)
    - SCOPE, London, England, 1980 March 28 (Box 83:424)
    - Burdick Elementary School, Stamford, CT, 1980 April 9 (Box 83:425)
    - Richardson School District, Richardson, Texas, 1980 April 20 (Box 83:426)
    - Shoreham-Wading Elementary School, NY, 1980 April 28 (Box 83:427)
    - Barlow Mountain Elementary School, CT, 1980 May 20 (Box 83:428)
    - ALA Doubleday's Local Authors & Illustrators, NY, 1980 June 30 (Box 83:429)
    - Lindenwood College, St. Charles, Missouri, 1980 July 7 (Box 83:430)
    - Commack Union Free School District, NY, 1980 October 1 (Box 83:431)
    - Stauffer Chemical Co. Art Show, Westport, CT, 1980 October 20 (Box 83:432)
    - Children's Book Guild, 1980 November 22 (Box 83:433)
    - Not finalized- LEF did not appear, 1981 (Box 83:434)
    - Los Angeles School Library Association, CA, 1981 February 22 (Box 83:435)
    - Los Angeles School Library Association, CA, 1981 February 26 (Box 83:436)
    - New Britain Museum of American Art, CT, 1981 March 11 (Box 83:437)
    - Fairfield University, Fairfield, CT, 1981 April 4 (Box 83:438)
    - Follet Book Co., Crystal Lake, Illinois, 1981 April 7 (Box 83:439)
    - Shoreham School District, Shoreham, NY, 1981 April 10 (Box 83:440)
    - Bethel Public Library, Bethel, CT, 1981 April 13 (Box 83:441)
    - Wheeler School, Plainville, CT, 1981 May 27 (Box 83:442)
    - Connecticut Book Festival, New Britain, CT, 1981 June 2 (Box 83:443)
    - Quest for Quality Program, Davenport, IA, 1981 June 10 (Box 83:444)
    - Kings Highway School, CT, 1981 June 16 (Box 83:445)
    - University of Minnesota, 1981 June 24 (Box 83:446)
    - Tolland, CT, 1981 November 5 (Box 83:447)
    - NCTE Convention, Boston, CT, 1981 November 21 (Box 83:448)
    - Not Finalized / LEF did not attend, 1982 (Box 83:449)
    - YWCA, Greenwich, CT, 1982 March 5 (Box 83:450)
    - Hamilton Avenue School, Greenwich, CT, 1982 March 29 (Box 83:451)
    - Eastbury School, Glastonbury, CT, 1982 April 13 (Box 83:452)
    - Bloomsburg St. College Reading Conference, PA, 1982 April 16 (Box 83:453)
    - Weston Middle School, Weston, CT, 1982 April 21 (Box 83:454)
    - IRA Convention, Frostburg, MD, 1982 April 24 (Box 83:455)
    - Appalachian State University, Boone, NC, 1982 July 5 (Box 83:456)
    - ALA Conference, Philadelphia, PA, 1982 July 9 (Box 83:457)
    - Holmes School, 1982 September 20 (Box 83:458)
    - Dallas Public Library, Dallas, Texas, 1982 September 24 (Box 83:459)
    - Museum of Art, Science & Industry, Bridgeport, CT, 1982 September 28 (Box 83:460)
    - Connecticut Reading Conference, 1982 October 16 (Box 83:461)
    - NYLA, Lockport, New York, 1982 October 23 (Box 83:462)
    - Mohegan School, Shelton, CT, 1982 November 16 (Box 83:463)
    - West Point Elementary School, West Point, NY, 1982 November 17 (Box 83:464)
    - Not finalized / LEF did not appear, 1983 (Box 84:465)
    - Ohio Young Authors, Columbus, Ohio, 1983 February 23 (Box 84:466)
    - Art place, Southport, CT, 1983 March 9 (Box 84:467)
    - South Carolina Association of School Libraries, 1983 April 7 (Box 84:468)
    - California State University, CA, 1983 April 15 (Box 84:469)
    - Miller Avenue School, Shoreham, NY, 1983 May 9 (Box 84:470)
    - Bradley School, Derby, CT, 1982 May 11 (Box 84:471)
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1983 August 1 (Box 84:472)
    - EVERYCHILD Conference, NY, 1983 August 29 (Box 84:473)
    - AAUW, Westport Public Library, Westport, CT, 1983 September 10 (Box 84:474)
    - Hamden Library, Hamden, CT, 1983 October 19 (Box 84:475)
    - Appalachian State University, Boone, NC, 1983 November 4 (Box 84:476)
    - Not finalized / LEF did not appear, 1984 (Box 84:477)
    - CSU, Fresno, CA, 1984 February 10 (Box 84:478)
    - San Diego Public Schools, San Diego, CA, 1984 February 21 (Box 84:479)
    - CMLEA, California, 1984 February 25 (Box 84:480)
    - Sinai Temple, Los Angeles, CA, 1984 February 26 (Box 84:481)
    - Roger Sherman School, Fairfield, CT, 1984 March 14 (Box 84:482)
    - Florida Atlantic University, 1984 April 11 (Box 84:483)
    - IRA, Atlanta, Georgia, 1984 May 6 (Box 84:484)
    - Noah Wallace School, Farmington, CT, 1984 May 16 (Box 84:485)
    - Ohio State University, 1984 May 18 (Box 84:486)
    - Stratford Academy, CT, 1984 May 30 (Box 84:487)
    - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1984 June 9 (Box 84:488)
    - Brigham Young University, Provo, Utah, 1984 June 18 (Box 84:489)
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1984 June 26 (Box 84:490)
    - New Jersey State Library, NJ, 1984 September 12 (Box 84:491)
    - Not finalized / LEF did not appear, 1985 (Box 84:492)
    - Naples Central School, New York, 1985 May (Box 84:493)
    - Lorain City Schools, Lorain, Ohio, 1985 May 3 (Box 84:494)
    - Jersey State Teachers College, Jersey City, NJ, 1985 October 30 (Box 84:495)
    - Everson Museum of Art, Syracuse, NY, 1985 November 17 (Box 84:496)
    - Lexington Public Schools, Lexington, MA, 1985 December 6 (Box 84:497)
    - List of appearances, 1986 (Box 84:498)
    - Not finalized / LEF did not appear, 1986 (Box 84:499)
    - White Rabbit Book Shop, La Jolla, CA, 1986 February 15 (Box 84:500)
    - Middle Gate School, Newton, CT, 1986 April 11 (Box 84:501)
    - IRA Convention, Philadelphia, PA, 1986 April 13 (Box 84:502)
    - Westport Public Schools, Westport, CT, 1986 May 19 (Box 84:503)
    - The Greenwich Art Show, Greenwich, CT, 1986 June 9 (Box 84:504)
    - ALA, New York, 1986 June 27 (Box 84:505)
    - Danbury Public Schools, Danbury, CT, 1986 August 21 (Box 84:506)
    - San Joaquin County Author's Symposium, CA, 1986 October 17 (Box 84:507)
    - Lincoln Unified School District, 1986 October 20 (Box 84:508)
    - Stockton Unified School District, CA, 1986 October 22 (Box 84:509)
    - Enid Public Schools, Enid, Oklahoma, 1986 October 24 (Box 84:510)
    - University of Oklahoma, Norman, Oklahoma, 1986 October 25 (Box 84:511)
    - Montclair Public Library, Montclair, NJ, 1986 November 10 (Box 84:512)
    - Darien's Men's Club, 1986 December 5 (Box 84:513)
    - List of appearances, 1987 (Box 85:514)
    - Y's Men's Club of Westport, 1987 January 8 (Box 85:516)
    - University of New Orleans, Lakefront, Louisiana, 1987 January 24 (Box 85:517)
    - Ohio State University, 1987 February 4 (Box 85:518)
    - Highland Park Elementary School, Grove City, OH, 1987 February 4 (Box 85:519)
    - Burbank Elementary School, Columbus, Ohio, 1987 February 5 (Box 85:520)
    - Michigan State University, 1987 February 28 (Box 85:521)
    - Rhode Island Educational Media Association, RI, 1987 March 10 (Box 85:522)
    - New Philadelphia Schools, New Philadelphia, OH, 1987 March 16 (Box 85:523)
    - Stratford Public Library, Stratford, CT, 1987 April 1 (Box 85:524)
    - Cider Mill School, Wilton, CT, 1987 April 8 (Box 85:525)
    - Michigan Library Association, Lansing, MI, 1987 May 1 (Box 85:526)
    - Woodstock Public Schools, Woodstock, CT, 1987 May 12 (Box 85:527)
    - Oklahoma State University, 1987 June 22 (Box 85:528)
    - Pennsylvania State University, Middletown, PA, 1987 June 30 (Box 85:529)
    - Central Arkansas Library System, Arkansas, 1987 October 10 (Box 85:530)
    - Southwestern CT Library Council, Westport, CT, 1987 October 28 (Box 85:531)
    - Southwestern CT Library Council, Westport, CT, 1987 November 15 (Box 85:532)
    - Old Trail School, Bath, Ohio, 1987 November 16 (Box 85:533)
    - IRA, Cuyahoga Summit Chapter, Ohio, 1987 November 17 (Box 85:534)
    - Stark County Library, Canton, Ohio, 1987 November 18 (Box 85:535)
    - SECLA Children's Book Festival, Old Lyme, CT, 1987 November 21 (Box 85:536)
    - List of appearances, 1988 (Box 85:537)
    - Not finalized / LEF did not appear, 1988 (Box 85:538)
    - Greenwich Country Day School, Greenwich, CT, 1988 January 20 (Box 85:539)
    - Ramona United and Valley Center Schools, CA, 1988 February 16 (Box 85:540)
    - Bluffton College, Bluffton, Ohio, 1988 February 25 (Box 85:541)
    - Sam Houston State University, Houston, Texas, 1988 March 18 (Box 85:542)
    - National Council Teachers of English, Boston, MA, 1988 March 25 (Box 85:543)
    - Western Illinois State University, Macomb, Iowa, 1988 April 8 (Box 85:544)
    - Geauga County Board of Education, Ohio, 1988 April 29 (Box 85:545)
    - Ferris State College, Big Rapids, Michigan, 1988 May 5 (Box 85:546)
    - IRA, Toronto, Canada, 1988 May 3 (Box 85:547)
    - Pequot Library Bookfest, CT, 1988 October 9 (Box 85:548)
    - SCBW, New York, 1988 November 5 (Box 85:549)
    - New Haven Public Schools, New Haven, CT, 1988 November 9 (Box 85:550)
    - Children's Book Council, New York, 1988 November 12 (Box 85:551)
    - CA Media and Library Educator's Association, CA, 1988 November 18 (Box 85:552)
    - Correspondence for appearances, 1989 (Box 85:553)
    - Correspondence for appearances, 1990 (Box 86:554)
    - Children's Literature Conference, Ohio State, 1990 January 25 (Box 86:555)
    - List of appearances, 1991 (Box 86:556)
    - Southern Connecticut Library Council, 1990-1991 (Box 86:557)
    - Denton Avenue School, New Hyde Park, 1991 February 6 (Box 86:558)
    - University of Minnesota: The Kerlan Award, 1991 April 30 (Box 86:559)
    - Rowayton Arts Center 1991 Studio Tour, 1991 April 27 (Box 86:560)
    - 6th Annual Young Author's Conference, OH, 1991 May 4 (Box 86:561)
    - New Haven Paint & Clay Club Annual, CT, 1991 May 6 (Box 86:562)
    - 36th Annual IRA Convention, 1991 May 6 (Box 86:563)
    - Parkway School District, Missouri, 1991 May 9 (Box 86:564)
    - 15th Annual Young Author's Festival, Michigan, 1991 May 11 (Box 86:565)
    - Huckleberry Hill Elementary School, CT, 1991 May 16 (Box 86:566)
    - Jacob Javits Center, NY - autograph session, 1991 June 3 (Box 86:567)
    - ALA, Atlanta, Georgia, 1991 June 28 (Box 86:568)
    - Whistle Stop Books, 1991 September 8 (Box 86:569)
    - Friends of Libraries special project meeting, CT, 1991 September 19 (Box 86:570)
    - Project D.R.E.A.M, The Foundry, New Haven, CT, 1991 October 22 (Box 86:571)
    - New York City School Volunteer Program, 1991 November (Box 86:572)
    - Rochester, NY, 1991 April 9 (Box 86:573)
    - List of Appearances, 1992 (Box 86:574)
    - Asa Packer Elementary School, Bethlehem, PA, 1992 February 20 (Box 86:575)
    - SCBW Conference for Writers, Massachusetts, 1992 March 7 (Box 86:576)
    - Maryland Educational Media Organization, MD, 1992 March 26 (Box 86:577)
    - Horace Mann Elementary School, WA, 1992 April 4 (Box 86:578)
    - Wichita's Public Schools, Wichita, Kansas, 1992 April 9 (Box 86:579)
    - Farmingville School, Ridgefield, CT, 1992 April 28 (Box 86:580)
    - Frostburg State University, MD, 1992 May 1 (Box 86:581)
    - UCONN Book Fair, 1992 May 3 (Box 86:582)
    - IRA Convention, Orlando, Florida, 1992 May 4 (Box 86:583)
    - Pickaway County Schools, Circleville, Ohio, 1992 May 15 (Box 86:584)
    - Bassett Book Store, Stamford, CT, 1992 July 17 (Box 86:585)
    - Silvermine Guild and Murphy School, Stamford, CT, 1992 October 16 (Box 86:586)
    - New Canaan Country Day School, New Canaan, CT, 1992 October 29 (Box 86:587)
    - New Haven Public Schools, Project DREAM, 1992 November 10 (Box 86:588)
    - List of appearances, 1993 (Box 86:589)
    - Not finalized / LEF did not appear, 1993 (Box 86:590)
    - Not finalized / LEF did not appear, 1993 February 10 (Box 86:591)
    - Phone interview from Emerson Magnet School, 1993 April 9 (Box 86:592)
    - Weld County Reading Association, Greeley, CO, 1993 April 22 (Box 86:593)
    - San Antonio, Texas, 1993 April 27 (Box 86:594)
    - Pennsylvania School Librarians Association, 1993 April 30 (Box 86:595)
    - NERA, 1993 October 29 (Box 86:596)
    - Jersey City State College, 1993 November 1 (Box 86:597)
    - Mill Hill Schools, Southport, CT, 1993 November 3 (Box 86:598)
    - Not finalized / LEF did not appear, 1994 (Box 87:599)
    - Southern Connecticut Library Council, 1994 (Box 87:600)
    - Central Missouri State University, Warrensburg, MI, 1994 (Box 87:601)
    - Horizon Middle School, Kearney, Nebraska, 1994 February (Box 87:602)
    - Nebraska State Reading Council, 1994 February 24 (Box 87:603)
    - Children's Literature Festival at CMSU, 1994 March 17 (Box 87:604)
    - Lansing, Michigan, 1994 March 23 (Box 87:605)
    - Massachusetts Reading Association Conference, 1994 April 7 (Box 87:606)
    - IRA, Toronto, 1994 May 12 (Box 87:607)
    - Westport Historical Society, CT, 1994 May (Box 87:608)
    - "Children's Authors & Illustrators" - t.v. show, 1994 June 8 (Box 87:609)
    - ALA, Miami, Florida, 1994 June 25 (Box 87:610)
    - Kerlan Collection Benefit, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1994 October 15 (Box 87:611)
    - Brooklyn Public Library, 1994 October 21 (Box 87:612)
    - University of Connecticut, 1994 November 5 (Box 87:613)
    - UCONN Co-op, Storrs, CT, 1994 November (Box 87:614)
    - Y's Women's Club, Westport, CT, 1994 November 28 (Box 87:615)
    - List of Appearances, 1995 (Box 87:616)
    - League of Women's Voters, Westport, CT, 1995 January 18 (Box 87:617)
    - Cooleytown Middle School, Westport, CT, 1995 February 2 (Box 87:618)
    - YMCA of Westport and Weston, CT,1995 February 9 (Box 87:619)
    - Senior Men's Club of New Canaan, CT, 1995 March 3 (Box 87:620)
    - Port Jefferson Elementary School, NY, 1995 March 15 (Box 87:621)
    - AAUW Meet the Author Committee, Trumbull, CT, 1995 April 2 (Box 87:622)
    - Whitehorne Middle School, Verona, NJ, 1995 April 6 (Box 87:623)
    - The Ellis School, Pittsburgh, PA, 1995 April 12 (Box 87:624)
    - Hope College, Holland, MI, 1995 April 20 (Box 87:625)
    - May Hill Arbuthnot Honor Lecture, 1995 May 5 (Box 87:626)
    - Madison Middle School, Trumbull, CT, 1995 May 9 (Box 87:627)
    - ALA Conference, Chicago, Illinois, 1995 June 23 (Box 87:628)
    - St. Anne's School, Bristol, Virginia, 1995 November 2 (Box 87:629)
    - Westport Public Library, 1995 November (Box 87:630)
    - Wayne State University, 1995 November 30 (Box 87:631)
    - List of appearances, 1996 (Box 87:632)
    - Y's Men's Club of Westport and Weston, CT, 1996 (Box 87:633)
    - Boston Public Library, 1996 January 11 (Box 87:634)
    - New Britain Museum, New Britain, CT, 1996 April 6 (Box 87:635)
    - CLA Conference, Cromwell, 1996 April 23 (Box 87:636)
    - IRA Convention, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1996 April 29 (Box 87:637)
    - Farmingville Elementary School, 1996 May 8 (Box 87:638)
    - Somers Intermediate School, Somers, NY, 1996 May 10 (Box 87:639)
    - ALA Conference, New York, NY, 1996 July 5 (Box 87:640)
    - St. Aloysius School, NY, 1996 September 27 (Box 87:641)